Guide to the Sheri Martinelli Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 1999 Acquisition, 1905-1993; 114.5; (127 boxes)+ 13 art, 1 broadside, 1 roll
  - Audiocassettes and Microcassettes, 1979-1993; Series VI; 78; (78 boxes)
    - Audiocassettes
      - "B/art tape original-Eva J+J erase Saturday 4/22/78", 1978 April 22; 1
      - "Talk from other side not too good Thrones scholar etc. to P/", undated; 1
      - "Moon justice sun justice EP Thrones scholar job new EP", undated; 1
      - "Thrones Cayce 3 states etc.", undated; 1
      - "7/14/81 on tape-kiss perfume", 1981 July 14; 1
      - "Check", undated; 1
      - "Mostly talk, men November 3, 1986 Virginia", 1986 November; 1
      - "Delta gor and maybe other side check", undated; 1
      - "gd 3 wish cycle/moon, sun/ scholar job talk", undated; 1
      - # 1-2 5/5/83 at P'ton B/T/sea, 1983 May 5; 2
      - "5/5/83 at P'ton B/T/Sea also DDS tech", 1983 May 5; 1
      - "May 11, 1983 Thrift store Mutts good and bad BF", 1983 May 11; 1
      - "Sunday, Saturday, Friday May 13-15, 1983 TITCD etc.", 1
      - "#2 BF", undated; 1
      - The Chemical Story by Dr. Bernard Jensen #1, Jensen's Nutritional & Health products, inc., undated; 1
      - Natural Healing by Dr. Bernard Jensen, #2, Jensen's Nutritional & Health Products, Inc., undated; 1
      - Building a Way to Eat by Dr. Bernard Jensen, #3, Jensen's Nutritional & Health Products, Inc., undated; 1
      - "Tape 101", undated; 1
      - "Started erase - T complaint home", undated; 1
      - "1 for you to answer June 11, 1978 Mother and geo. 2 answer f home", 1978 June 11; 1 (Box 110)
      - "I talk at night of creek home to G.M. and A. Lilly copied from home 2 en route to work stops here and blank rest", undated; 1
      - "#1 Listening to tape from home and talking to it. S&F ", undated; 1
      - "Libel case, April 16, 1982 after rest some last", 1982 April 16; 5
      - "Delta G 10/5/81 Monday", 1981 October 5; 1
      - "11/25/81", 1981 November 25; 1
      - "Driving to storage rain-ish", undated; 1
      - "Wednesday morning 7/13/83 Bible prophecy", 1983 July 13; 1
      - "Saturday 7/9/83 Wednesday 7/13/83 music", 1983 July 9; 1
      - "sch erase", undated; 1
      - "Laurel + stars Mormons 2 Laurels", undated; 1
      - "1/L", undated; 1
      - "2/L", undated; 1
      - "1 4pm Thursday 6/1/78 spoke from T/other? original 2 original baby notes", 1978 June 1; 1
      - "1 noon Thursday 6/1/78/ JE child original", 1978 June 1; 1
      - "Copy for original re: How to Raise a Child to JE Sheri SM", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2 (Box 111)
      - "Delta G 2/16/82 3", 1982 February 16; 1
      - "DDS etc. Delta G 2/16/82 2 of 3", 1982 February 16; 1
      - "Thursday 6/16/83 Wednesday 6/22/83 Sorcery Creek", 1983 June; 1
      - "Wednesday 6/22/83 negative positive o/c", 1983 June 22; 1
      - "Thursday 6/9/83 kookoo/G at end", 1983 June 9; 1
      - "At of IZ Saturday 6/11/83 only like Moses page 6/12/83 Sunday", 1983 June 11; 1
      - "An 'Index' (of sub mat to emerge) tape", undated; 1
      - "T/creek half moon lib giggle and Rus Scientist", undated; 1
      - "Talk at [illegible] and G/attack on Tuesday night May 24 to B/F 8am Grange truck Thursday 5/26/83", 1983 May; 1
      - "TIT CT and birds charity", undated; 1
      - "Salt first side 2 second anger as a tool or key or weapon, Salt #1", undated; 2
      - "Delta G 2/16/82 #1 of 3 DDS-acct-abt half wa?", 1982 February 16; 1
      - "Test 3/30/82", 1982 March 30; 1
      - "#1/ #2", undated; 1
      - "April 26, 1982 abuse", 1982 April 26; 1
      - "May 1", undated; 1
      - "On tape to here", undated; 1
      - "On tape", undated; 1
      - "One side", undated; 1 (Box 112)
      - "5/5/83 at Princeton by T/sea other mat", 1983 May 5; 1
      - "AAA", undated; 1
      - "YR comments off tape x1A portrait of T/ artist as an American citizen talk X1B cycle sound and talk", undated; 1
      - "X1E", undated; 1
      - "Talk (Helly/Hin) longer version brings own family in also x1c to x1d case", undated; 1
      - "Holly Hin Turkey 6900 10 year olds "geetar" 3 wks on end and 1 long version sound version Talk x1D", undated; 1
      - "Noise second tape sound", undated; 1
      - "Cycle/noise/short recording", undated; 1
      - "From Sunday February 1, 1987 SM tape early morning talk church about drugs etc. Sanyo copy", 1987 February 1; 1
      - "#1 May 5-7, 1983 Saturday Sunday B/F", 1983 May 1; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Notes Monday May 2 23 83", 1983 May 2; 1
      - "Playing game Irene?", undated; 1
      - "Listen", undated; 1
      - "From SM tape 6/7/87 T/ugh", 1987 June 7; 1
      - "Out of Machine-California tape", undated; 1
      - "Neera", undated; 1
      - "T/driving schools of T/future for Mrs. Fishman", undated; 1
      - "S argument old", undated; 1 (Box 113)
      - "April 25 or so not finished yet", undated; 1
      - "Monday 8/22/83 fr. lawyer end", 1983 August 22; 1
      - "Keep for Sheri 79 August", 1979 August; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Sunday 8/7/83 get Maxie T/case", 1983 August 7; 1
      - "8/7/83 Sun fight", 1983; 1
      - "Sunday/Mon August 14-15, 1983/St. Louis August 13 fight", 1983 August; 1
      - "Friday 7/29/83 listen to end Trucks", 1983 July 29; 1
      - "8/6/83 Maxie", 1983 August 6; 1
      - "August 2, 1982 T/unemployed and judge and work etc. are in here part of file not so vital. Note on DP and with Lewis Art", 1982 August 2; 1
      - "Pension plan information by Lib 2 pm July 16, 1982", 1982 July 16; 1
      - "at offiz talk, Thursday", 1983 June 16; 1
      - "Prayer Ta She Mone Chattau Wednesday", 1983 June 22; 1
      - "2 pm Friday 6/24/83", 1983 June 24; 1
      - "Drive tape", undated; 1
      - "Drive", undated; 1
      - "copy Sheri/Tina/Jon etc. a beg for file", undated; 1
      - "Case/file/items/started May 22, 1983 Sunday 2 pm copy/tape", 1983 May 22; 1
      - "Saturday morning May 21, 1983 at of IZ", 1983 May 21; 1
      - "Music Pan Celtic fr SM tape PAN\Celtic", undated; 1
      - "Saturday May 21, 1983 and Sunday May 22, 1983 on index tape of sub mat to emerge Downtown S/F B/F T/noise from downtown SF -excuse-", 1983 May; 1 (Box 114)
      - "Listen", 1978; 1
      - "Carroll", undated; 1
      - "This side off fr new", undated; 1
      - "You Chi Jon 10/17/78", 1978 October 10; 1
      - "Jon 12 midnight pictures in BK kings", undated; 1
      - "Omit", undated; 1
      - John Denver's Greatest Hits RCA records, 1973; 1
      - "2nd on", undated; 1
      - "5/20/83", 1983 May 20; 1
      - "Copied fr SM tapes 10/29/85 brakes one", 1985 October 29; 1
      - "Copy from small tape", undated; 1
      - "Noise records R shack tape", undated; 1
      - "Noise from Panosonic plays SM tape", undated; 1
      - "FR SM tapes talk G or D produce", undated; 1
      - "Farmers idea MaZ do over", undated; 1
      - "From SM tape 9talk0 JAZ Q\good listen again Tailless monkeys galleries end of JAZ/terr/Pete talk from SM tape and rest clear genius/T/poor/Life death", undated; 1
      - "American education male account of St/ cycle Sunday", 1986 November 1; 1
      - "From SM tapes #2 side 1 Rainbow papers side 2 on driving hear last part again humanity 3 that form etc"., undated; 1
      - "t/sound/7/Friday/17/81 see layer", 1981; 1
      - "Wednesday 4:20 pm", 1981 July 15; 1
      - "scav's/no rock of 12 Kasho valentines", 1983 July 7; 1 (Box 115)
      - "Saturday 7/9/83", 1983 July 9; 1
      - "Scorcery", 1983 July 6; 1
      - "Move Trl/SP and NJ G/S survey mother place/from SM tapes", undated; 1
      - "Sunday S+M S", 1983 December 4; 1
      - 1/24/84 S+S, 1
      - "Allen birthday 1984", 1
      - "Copy A/B/day", 1984 January 24; 1
      - "To S/Moore 11/24/83 S Moore 11/22/83 listen/erase", 1983 November; 1
      - "St-M 1983", 1
      - "On Va Rd Sunday", 1983 August 21; 1
      - "Monday 8/18/83 lock car door", 1983 August 18; 1
      - "Friday 8/19/83 see legal aid for Wednesday soma ZLSD", undated; 1
      - "Tuesday August 16, 1983 Wednesday LSD", 1983 August 19; 1
      - "8/15/83 lock door Monday 8/14/83", 1983 August 14; 1
      - "Monday 8/22/83/Sunday", 1983 August; 1
      - "At Atl Cty Lib grounds Sunday October 9, 1983 October 10, 1983 T/credit or cash for work done and test 1 money", 1
      - "read drive bk 9/17/83 Monday DMV/mother testimony", 1983 October; 1
      - "Mother, monday, DMV", 1983 October 17; 1
      - "Chandler", 1983 August 10; 1
      - "Not used, no register sound", undated; 1
      - "8/8/83 fighting", 1983 August 8; 1 (Box 116)
      - "6/27/83 9:30 fiery chants", 1983 June 27; 1
      - "Sunday 6/26/83", 1983 June 26; 1
      - "June 28-29, 1983 T/prayer", 1983 June; 1
      - "Bumper hitch 6/30/83 7/1/83", 1983; 1
      - "6/28/29/30 hitch and etc. 7/1/83", 1983; 1
      - "7/3/83 Sunday 7/5/83 slmeO of 12", 1983 July; 1
      - "7/5/83 Tuesday 7/6/83", 1983 July; 1
      - "Vision Thursday 6/23/83", 1983 June; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "(Bank) Saturday 6/25/83 D.A.", 1983 June 25; 1
      - "Sunday 6/26/83", 1983; 1
      - "Friday 6/24/83 TITct and EP Pope perception", 1983 June 24; 1
      - "T/pkg lot TLC and shop Loewdy", undated; 1
      - "Family negative complaint", undated; 1
      - "T. Hardy/HD/EP/DP", undated; 1
      - "ESP EXP", undated; 1
      - "Monday February 6, 1984 ends suddenly", 1984 February 6; 1
      - "Copy fr. J+L tape 2/6/84", 1984 February 6; 1
      - "T/tape not good", undated; 1
      - "Monday 5/23/83 Noise of traffic and/or motor\freeway etc. SF scraps B/F", 1983 May 23; 1 (Box 117)
      - "11:15", undated; 1
      - "Cont", undated; 1
      - "1 JC erase", undated; 1
      - "Original was copied check copy then erase", undated; 1
      - "Fone SM/DRGM Billy/Gand M ZXN copy batteries low on other discuss Virginia and California Medicade 87.a Dg other copy on P of A phone tape", undated; 1
      - "Fone 6/14/92 SWN St/M about dealer", 1992 June 14; 1
      - "Fone California Copy of P of A 1990/ bad not right/Virginia laws 6/19/92 California G and M/Lawyer battery ran out/silly sounds redo on other tape", 1992 June 19; 1
      - "Noon or 12:30 pm to 1:00 6/13/92 M and G and GWL Saturday/M and G California phone", 1992 June 13; 1
      - "Fone St/M from Sunday 6/14/92 entire tape explaining should be St/M", 1992 June 14; 1
      - "Fone "looks down on people" E.L./M and GW/copy of phone re house Friday 6/12/92 Nancy Kovick", 1992 June 12; 1
      - "September 23, 1984", 1984 September 23; 1
      - "P", undated; 1
      - "Original", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Monday September 27, 1993; 9:35 AM, rainish #1 Sheri's dreams of M de RR", 1993 September 27; 1
      - "Dreams #2", undated; 1
      - "Where the grapes of wrath are whored #1", undated; 1
      - "Where the grapes of wrath are whored #2", undated; 1
      - "Talk Art Letters, etc. Friday 9/23/93 9/24/93", 1993 September; 1
      - "T/herb sit/Monday 9/23/93, T/phone message", 1993 September 23; 1
      - "T/case house G/fr. lawyer T/or S.S. loan at beginning some T.V. Ind Bl. Hills", undated; 1 (Box 118)
      - "Case/house solstice 12/22/91", 1991 December 22; 1
      - "T.V. chanting?", undated; 1
      - "?", undated; 1
      - "Culture? etc.", undated; 1
      - "On tape Friday August 24, 1990", 1990 August 24; 1
      - "Day 21/solstice summer; Day 22/Monday for lawyer. Phone noise #2 tape; phone repair man came to fix phone", undated; 1
      - "Day 22-23 June 1992 for lawyer solstice week #2 tape, 1992 June; 1
      - "Day 23 June 1992, Tuesday to end, for lawyer solstice week #2 tape", 1992 June; 1
      - "Lady M", undated; 1
      - "In order to arrive at Mind's center genetic code and T's canto comp/11th commandment and gossip/genetic code #1 core", undated; 1
      - "Channel 32 and SM talks 8 pm, speaks of Anne Besant", undated; 1
      - "T/condition of being "all" and why?", undated; 1
      - "Imitate/December 4, Friday 1992 Freedom and slavery SM talk", 1992 December; 1
      - "Stolic E/St/Va", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "Eva", undated; 1
      - "On tape Eva PBK etc.", undated; 1
      - "To Eva start Saturday August 3, 1991 5:45 PM V.V. Hot Daye", 1991 August 3; 1
      - "Eva /art etc. #1 of 2/Monday/Tuesday/ Wednesday week of May 18-20, 1992", 1992 May; 1 (Box 119)
      - "Eva Wednesday May 20, 1992 art talk #2 of 2 Eva/SM", 1992 May; 1
      - "To Eva Monday May 4, 1992 from SM; SM art etc. #A-1; Eva/SM 5:05 PM/D.S.T.", 1992 May 4; 1
      - "April 12, 1993 Eva", 1993 April 12; 1
      - "April 12, 1993 A gov", 1993 April 12; 1
      - "Writer etc.. April 23, 1993", 1993 April 23; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Neighborhood acts/Saturday June 20, 1992 3 pm and on Bk yd sudden noise?", 1992 June 20; 1
      - "SM, part of her will untimely demise", undated; 1
      - "Lawyer type tape SM/ill G negelct June 19, 1992 Friday", 1992 June 19; 1
      - "Off to send or select for or to P/R #2 Wednesday September 22, 1993 #1", 1993 Spetember 22; 1
      - "To send or not to P/R Wednesday 9/22/93 #1", 1993 September 22; 1
      - "2 copies of 9/22/93", 1993 September 22; 1
      - "Sunday August 4, 1991 G vile on G/ beginning Sunday August 4, 1991-account of abuse", 1991 August; 1
      - "On tape", undated; 1
      - "No alcohol except on his own time", undated; 1
      - "S+M re October 5. 11/14/85/track", 1985; 1
      - "SM god/religion #1A", undated; 1
      - "#2A", undated; 1
      - "Mr. T and quote #1", undated; 1
      - "Mr. T and quote #2", undated; 1 (Box 120)
      - "SM T.V. first part of T/Republican Convention", undated; 1
      - "Joeie-Bambino", undated; 1
      - "Mr. B'bk Rev 10/15/92//T\Cat Inside NOC/MS #2 allen DRM", 1992 October 15; 1
      - "Shouts 1/P/ 11/19/90 #1", 1990 November 19; 1
      - "Shouts 2P #2 11/21/90", 1990 November 21; 1
      - "Shouts 1P #3", undated; 1
      - "Talk #1 Photographs of T/Mind", undated; 2
      - "Joie talk", 1990; 1
      - "Talk 1/16/90", 1990 January 16; 1
      - "Talk? on tape", undated; 1
      - "P+B", undated; 1
      - "BACI", undated; 1
      - "AOP Maz fr. Boce HD Poltergeists AOP fr BACI", undated; 1
      - "P/?", undated; 1
      - "P/finish", undated; 1
      - "P/same copy from other tapes including December 28, 1989 Friday answer P's (I think)", 1989 December 28; 1
      - "P/answer to letter? 15.15.89 whut's AT ? P answer sort of latest letter Sheri", 1989; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "1/3/90 Wednesday Pandemic Kulch or Kulche west world", 1990 January 3; 1 (Box 121)
      - "Prophecy/art #1 & #2", undated; 2
      - "T/visit and T/visitation Wednesday #1 & #2", 1991 January 9; 2
      - "Listen type #1-3 /SM", undated; 3
      - "Sunday 23, 1991 8 AM on re St/M proposed BK", 2
      - "To St. M from SM re: proposed bk", 1991 March 20; 1
      - "SM talk", undated; 1
      - "Mr. T idea audio and/or video Monday", 1991 January 2; 1
      - "SM gen talk on tape", undated; 1
      - "Too fast?", undated; 1
      - "#1", undated; 1
      - "Start D ToP/", undated; 1
      - "P/SM #2", undated; 1
      - "P and E from Sheri Monday", 1991 May 27; 1
      - "Visits on hold/exorcism and NAZCA CHACO/T/lights and scare go off 4/14/81 #1", 1981 April 14; 1
      - "NAZCA lines #2", undated; 1
      - "Delta G 1", undated; 1 (Box 122)
      - "??? sound", undated; 1
      - "SM talk t/rest is Dross", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "SM talk Nicholas and Michael and Zen contemplation", undated; 1
      - "SM/talk Nicholas Apollo Dionesius", undated; 1
      - "SM talk energy last 30 years after/ mind states", undated; 1
      - "T/mother/Breath a note", undated; 1
      - "P re word ugh", undated; 1
      - "P", undated; 1
      - "Coyote howl 2 times from tape to P and E/ R.E. maybe T.V.", undated; 1
      - "T.V. from T.V. sand pictures Indian Navajo Ireland", undated; 1
      - "EP reading and SM comments", undated; 1
      - "Ezra Pound: Poems", undated; 1
      - "SM talk Pai A.E. test D", undated; 1
      - [Illegible] "of Maher", undated; 1
      - "September 9, 1984 phone call", 1984 September 9; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Driving inst.", undated; 1
      - "Drive tape qc-drive by", undated; 1
      - "List HONI SOIT/MADRE NOSTRA hear and erase", 1987 September 4; 1 (Box 123)
      - "FR SM tape\hear and erase not real good", undated; 1
      - "EP Dawoo", undated; 1
      - "Insp talk T\belief", undated; 1
      - "Talk", undated; 1
      - " P", 1986 December 8; 1
      - "S+M", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Fone Saturday 4 July, 1992 about 4ish M/G/Cal E's new place", 1992 July 4; 1
      - "SM/song/etc.", undated; 1
      - "TV and sound", undated; 1
      - "on tape 1", undated; 2
      - "Love" a-1, a-2, undated; 2
      - "Impressions from DP's birthday", undated; 1
      - "Notes from other tapes", 1984 September 16; 1
      - "Same day", undated; 1
      - "On tape M and O and art", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Copy 2, red bone Sanyo copy from record", undated; 1 (Box 124)
      - "Redbone side 1 of Potlach copy from Marantz", undated; 1
      - "Redbone copy Marantz Potlach copy from record", undated; 1
      - "Thursday August 12, 1993 about 1 Cott Rd #1", 1993 August 12; 1
      - "P/Russell wash X's 2 articles 5/21/93 #1", 1993 May 21; 1
      - "Cookson/T. Scott and Russell Sir W. Scott 5/21/93 #2", 1993 May 21; 2
      - "Tuesday 17, 1993 50s- Boci #1 & 2", 2
      - "Law stress (do paper on)", undated; 1
      - "West Cott Rd 1:30 pm Monday August 24, 1993 T/feel of it", 1993 August 24; 1
      - "J'ellen "My Quan Yin Child" and copy You Chi Joy Too", undated; 1
      - "My Quan Yin Child fr Juana original", undated; 1
      - "Ch poems Juana copy "My Quan Yin Child", undated; 1
      - "About Cayce F. 1/2/87 P/E", 1987 January 2; 1
      - "SM talk her house play", undated; 1
      - "List Honi's prayer death card letters", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Talk EP eval 9/4/87", 1987 September 4; 1
      - "Catch thots", undated; 1
      - "To all re t/papers listen", undated; 1 (Box 125)
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Memory", undated; 1
      - "To Louis at end", undated; 1
      - "#1", undated; 1
      - "Listen to V. beg only a few line erase", undated; 1
      - [Unlabelled], undated; 2
      - "To/z H+N in answer/SM", undated; 1
      - "faints copy beg Lee Bx 1044 Pacifica Cal", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Ch poetry,Test static", undated; 1
      - "Ch poetry/original", undated; 1
      - "Grief/Turq copy", undated; 1
      - "EP/erase and listen/talk with God and Green garden copy", undated; 1
      - "c/copy", undated; 1
      - "copy/SM/see note to P/mailed 1/13/87 tuesday 12/22/86", 1986-1987; 1
      - "Check this out", undated; 1
      - "T/artist and etc.", undated; 1
      - "Side #1 on tape", undated; 1
      - "On tape 2/4/92", 1992 February 4; 1 (Box 126)
      - "Talk Bk #1", undated; 1
      - "Talk #2 7/25/85", 1985 July 25; 1
      - "Farmers listen to fr beg", undated; 1
      - "Listen erase t/problem over-fast or slow", undated; 1
      - "Sharon 2/18/92 listen and edit", 1992 February 18; 1
      - "T/fld man is now 12/21/91", 1991 December 21; 1
      - "Monday Jan 20, 1992 SM talk fr self/T/ Chimu", 1992 January 20; 1
      - "At end Gloria mass", undated; 1
      - "SM talk/listen edit/ T/2 half moon's etc. to date", undated; 1
      - "Sunday February 9, 1992 talk to self #2 art", 1992 February 9; 1
      - "December 8, 1986", 1986 December 8; 1
      - "Catch all", undated; 1
      - "P+S", undated; 1
      - "Bl Swan", undated; 1
      - "Cookson", undated; 1
      - "Terr", undated; 2
      - "McCoy SM Sunday August 30, 1987 talk! talk! talk!", 1987 August 30; 1
      - "P/different mind state", undated; 1
      - "SM to recall (so as) abt September 5, 1992", 1992 September 5; 1 (Box 127)
      - "Cosmos 1/4/92/Saturday (miss beginning)", 1992; 1
      - "Joseph C. Myths/Time 1-3/92 Friday", 1992 January 3; 1
      - "Tiger and Lamb/SM memories of 1934 EP (some of)/part Joseph C Friday 1/3/92", 1992 January 3; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "TDH", undated; 3
      - "Art TDH", undated; 1
      - "G and ugly scene", 1988 May 25; 1
      - "P/June 4, 1989", 1989 June 4; 1
      - "P/Sat June 3, 1989", 1989 June 3; 1
      - "P/at long last a tape end of Isami", undated; 1
      - "Antigone Oedipus", undated; 4
      - "To self as to why of it #1 Saturday Sunday morning", undated; 1
      - "P commentary on tape "15.15.89" (and a strange)", 1989; 1 (Box 128)
      - "St/stanford EP paper father", undated; 1
      - "St Stanford 2", undated; 1
      - "a1 no #3", undated; 1
      - "Rameses II", 1990 February 16; 1
      - "Corridos", undated; 1
      - "X", undated; 1
      - "On tape? Bl. Elk Hoop", undated; 1
      - "#1 P got to v. end and didn't go on 1/2 hour", undated; 1
      - "Gonna be 1/2 hour", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Consultation re DR test 12 HR fast and appt. time 12/93", 1993 December; 1
      - "In t/mind state of poetry/fr. Anne C. side A=9/9/93 11 pm", 1993 September; 1
      - "Remembering SM Sunday September 12, 1993", 1993 September 12; 1
      - "Ann to", undated; 1
      - "3/4 used 10/2/88 Antigone tape caught stuck test 3", 1988 October 2; 1
      - "TV Antigone 10/2/88 good tape 3", 1988 October 2; 1
      - "Zen talk/West Cott noise", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Fone call after P", undated; 1
      - "Phone call Sunday 2/25/90", 1990; 1
      - "dos/pos/arouse neg/September 23 Sunday 90 T/wind lone TV/poem", undated; 1 (Box 129)
      - "R man", undated; 1
      - "O/S", undated; 2
      - "R/D 1-3", undated; 3
      - "Test it", undated; 1
      - "T/Cantos EP's letters", undated; 1
      - "All kinds sub matter tape #1", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 5
      - "To j1", undated; 1
      - "Play and test", undated; 1
      - "Continued on tape 1-A as marked and explained as to why March 6-90 Tuesday listen first", 1990 March 6; 1
      - "On tape P/better day after daughter half moon 7/14/89", 1989 July 14; 1
      - "On tape at ? M. tape", undated; 1
      - "SM to self re: self, Friday", 1993 October 15; 1
      - "P/abt 7/17/89", 1989 July 17; 1 (Box 130)
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "P and E 1-3 9/16/88", 1988 September 16; 3
      - "Sharon 10/7-8 or 9/88", 1988; 1
      - "Friday 11/11/88", 1988 November 11; 1
      - "Saturday 11/12/88 P", 1988 November 12; 1
      - "Sunday November 13, 1988", undated; 1
      - "J1 Sunday 8/6/89", 1989 August 6; 1
      - "Linda Ronstadt/pop. mat. only SM rec. re-use", undated; 1
      - "KAENITES/SHEM Friday 9/3/93", 1993 September 3; 1
      - "Side 1 Willi 10/10/88 #1", 1988 October 10; 1
      - "u/t/west world kulch item 1/3/90", 1990 January 3; 1
      - "w/w/ kulch", undated; 1
      - "after t/DDS visit/Elizabeth", undated; 1
      - "DDS scene same as #1 only on w it", undated; 1
      - "Reading 9/19/90", 1990 September 19; 1
      - "Return from Dr. visit / Elizabeth", 1990 September 19; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Sunday 5/7/89 cat food scenario fr Martin to lawyer", 1989 May 7; 1 (Box 131)
      - "Out of Sanya", undated; 1
      - "P/Sunday", undated; 1
      - "P before H-Da flue", undated; 1
      - "P#3", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 6
      - "Sunday war", 1983 July 17; 1
      - "7/18/83 Monday Marshall was here", 1983 July 18; 2
      - "7/26/83 Tuesday Mt. Denert", 1983 July 26; 2
      - "TAWLK 10/10 and on/88 UFO's 10/14/88 Friday DDS", 1988 October; 1
      - "#2 UFO's and TAWLK 10/14/88", 1988 October 14; 1
      - "Saturday August 28, 1993 Phone/DRG'mom /Honey/2x Maria", 1993 August 28; 1
      - "#1 U.T. on farewell words, undated; 2